(cans rattling)
(upbeat music)
♪ He was a boy ♪
♪ She was a girl ♪
♪ Can I make it any more obvious ♪
♪ He was a punk ♪
♪ She did ballet ♪
♪ What more can I say ♪
♪ He wanted her ♪
♪ She'd never tell ♪
♪ Secretly she wanted him as well ♪
♪ But all of her friends ♪
♪ Stuck up their nose ♪
♪ They had a problem
with his baggy clothes ♪
♪ He was a skater boy ♪
♪ She said, see you later, boy ♪
♪ He wasn't good enough for her ♪
♪ She had a pretty face ♪
♪ But her head was up in space ♪
♪ She needed to come back down to earth ♪
♪ Five years from now ♪
♪ She sits at home ♪
♪ Feeding the baby, she's all alone ♪
♪ She turns on TV ♪
♪ Guess who she sees ♪
♪ Skater boy rockin' up MTV ♪
♪ She calls up her friends ♪
♪ They already know ♪
♪ And they've all got
tickets to see his show ♪
♪ She tags along ♪
♪ And stands in the crowd ♪
♪ Looks up at the man
that she turned down ♪
♪ He was a skater boy ♪
♪ She said, see you later, boy ♪
♪ He wasn't good enough for her ♪
♪ Now he's a super star ♪
♪ Slammin' on his guitar ♪
♪ Does your pretty face
see what he's worth ♪
♪ He was a skater boy ♪
♪ She said, see you later, boy ♪
♪ He wasn't good enough for her ♪
♪ Now he's a super star ♪
♪ Slammin' on his guitar ♪
♪ Does your pretty face
see what he's worth ♪
(upbeat music continues)
♪ Sorry, girl, but you missed out ♪
♪ Well, tough luck that boy's mine now ♪
♪ We are more than just good friends ♪
♪ This is how the story ends ♪
♪ Too bad that you couldn't see ♪
♪ See the man that boy could be ♪
♪ There is more than meets the eye ♪
♪ I see the soul that is inside ♪
♪ He's just a boy ♪
♪ And I'm just a girl ♪
♪ Can I make it any more obvious ♪
♪ We are in love ♪
♪ Haven't you heard ♪
♪ How we rock each other's world ♪
♪ I'm with the skater boy ♪
♪ I said, see you later, boy ♪
♪ I'll be back stage after the show ♪
♪ I'll be at the studio ♪
♪ Singing the song we wrote ♪
♪ About a girl you used to know ♪
♪ I'm with the skater boy ♪
♪ I said, see you later, boy ♪
♪ I'll be back stage after the show ♪
♪ I'll be at the studio ♪
♪ Singing the song we wrote ♪
♪ About a girl you used to know ♪
(sirens blaring)